

NGUYỄN THỊ KHÁNH LY

khanhly.2k02@gmail.com.

© 0971031885

94/12, Street 14, BHHA Ward, Binh Tan District, HCM City.

OBJECTIVES

"Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it". I am always proactive in learning, diligent in researching to improve my skills and maintain a positive mindset. I always strive to become more professional to identify opportunities in Merchandise and bring more valued to myself and organizations.

EDUCATION

University of Economics and Law, VNU-HCM

2020 - 09/2024

- Major: Economic Mathematics (Business Analysis)
- Graduation ranking: Very Good
- Achievement:

Top 3 scientific research awards of the Faculty of Mathematics and Economics 2023.

Top 8 UEL young researcher competition (published in the international newspaper SR ICYREB International Conference) The Most Favorite Research Paper Award 2023.

Gold medal for 5 Good Students in 2021.

UEL Scholarship for the academic year 2021-2022, 2020-2021.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Thien Ngan Film Joint Stock Company Purchasing F&B Executive 10/2024 - Now

- Category Development, Sourcing Suppliers/Partners:
- Building and maintaining long-lasting relationships with suppliers/ partners to achieve revenue targets, develop the product assortment. Contacting negotiating with supplier.
- Analyzing market trends, products and competitor activities in market (Tea & Packaging & Coffee). Sourcing and executing negotiation beneficial commercial agreements with suppliers/partners.
- Carrying out purchasing procedures:
- Follow up stock and production planning to calculate, balance quantity
- Follow up to maket payment for orders.
- Follow up real raw material quantity arrive, delivering process.
- Collaborating and Solving Problem With Suppliers/Partners:
- Updating the quantity and status of existing inventory and coordinating with relevant departments and partners to control stock.
- Handling daily operations including orders, promotions, pricing, and issue resolution.
- Handling defective goods, recalled goods, returned goods with Suppliers. Checking product information and import price.



Pharmacity Pharmaceutical Joint Stock Company Merchandiser (Intern) 1/2024 - 5/2024

- Category Development, Sales Planning:
- Analyzing market trends and competitor activities in retail field.
- Negotiating and coordinating with suppliers to resolve customer issues effectively.
- Monitoring sales performance and managing trade contracts. Developing promotion proposals to achieve sales targets.
- Reporting, analyzing product assortments performance and developing sales plans to identify business needs and achieve KPI.
 - Collaborating and Sourcing Suppliers/Partners:
- Finding potential suppliers and products according to the company's category development strategy and policies.

- Working with all other cross-functional teams to ensure each campaign happen as guidelines.
- Coordinating the implementation plan for ordering to suppliers and handle arising issues.
- Carrying out purchasing procedures:
- Working directly with Clients and internal departments for inventory controls and evenue targets.
- Monitoring the delivery process of suppliers to relevant departments in the company and handle arising issues.
- Coordinating with other departments to carry out purchasing, receive purchase requests from relevant departments in the company. Create records to track ordering and purchasing from suppliers (Time, quantity...)



MASAN GROUP (Wincommerce) Strategy - Business Development Category (Intern Winmart)

7/2023 - 12/2023

- Category Development, Monitoring Stock and Sales Planning:
- Analyzing and reporting the brand/category performance, sales, stock in the Winmart chain and optimizing assortment.
- Responsible for monthly/yearly Commercial planning (KPI of display sales, KPI of promotion sales) to boost store revenue.
- Tracking and evaluating promotion activities & sales activities to propose new sales plan achieve sales target.
- Conducting market research and analysis to identify potential product opportunities and trends in the retail industry.
- Market & Competitor Tracking and Collaborating With Suppliers:
- Conducting market research of competitors, complaints and feedbacks to gain insights into customer problem.
- Collaborating with Trade Marketing, Operation & Marketing team to ensure each campaign happen as guidelines.
- Negotiating and promoting cooperation with suppliers to organize sampling/ activation in stores and Product pricing, sales and promotion to achieve sales.
 - Partnership Development:
- Coordinating with brands to implement sales support activities (vouchers, promotional programs,...).
- Searching for partners/suppliers that fit the sales plan. Organizing marketing activities to introduce the Hi! Beauty chain or new products (tiktok clips, workshops, webinars,...).

PROFESSIONAL SKILL









- · Strong Analytical Skills.
- · Organizing and Time-Management Skills
- · Negotiation and Collaboration Skills.
- · Strong Problem Solving and Research Skills.

LANGUAGES

English Toeic Listening & Reading: B2 (Certificate IIG VietNam)
 Toeic Speaking & Writing: 300 / 400 (Certificate IIG VietNam)

ACTIVITES

- · Member of Smile Gift SG Volunteer Club.
- Spring Volunteer Campaign 2022 Traditional Tet flavor.
- Project: Exploring factors influencing job satisfaction of employees during the digital era.
- Project: Forecasting drug product development at Pharmacity chain.
- Project: Forecast of Vinamilk's business revenue after the end of the Covid 19 pandemic

EXP: - Team work skills.

- Interpersonal skills.